Brandon Davidson

A dedicated team member with a focused work ethic

Santee, CA 92071 bdavidson112@gmail.com 6192538728

4 years of leadership and personnel management experience through the U.S. Army. Always striving for personal growth; having an open mind keeps me in constant learning mode. Being a part of a rapidly growing start up tech company keeps me on my toes and ever flexible for whatever task might come my way.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Technical Support Manager

LensLock Inc.-Poway, CA July 2022 to Present

- Monitoring the company fleet of servers and docking stations
- Database editing
- Troubleshooting customer issues (Call center, product repair)
- Product building (i.e. Docking Stations, Micro computing systems)
- Product configuration (i.e. Cameras, Docking Stations, Mini PCs, Servers, DVR)
- Video storage management
- In person user training
- Technical support employee management
- Internal Employee training
- Product install and transportation
- Research and Development of new product
- QA technician (software and hardware)
- Reporting to Engineering department

Customer Service Representative

LensLock Inc.-Poway, CA June 2020 to July 2022

- Call center hardware and software troubleshooting
- Device Monitoring
- Support website and email monitoring
- · Live Chat general agent
- Tier 1 and 2 technical support
- General and Admin user training
- Client knowledge base creation
- Customer success check-ups
- Critical info and video redaction

13B Cannon Crewmember

U.S. ARMY

July 2016 to November 2019

- Operated and maintained 5-ton howitzers
- Educated new personnel at my company about proper rifle marksmanship
- Uses computer generated data for effective fire direction
- Support team members in promoting organizational goals
- Utilize effective communication and interpersonal skills
- Critical thinking to develop solutions
- Services hydraulic, pneumatic, and electromechanical systems

Education

High school or equivalent

Steele Canyon High School - Rancho San Diego, CA

Skills

- Communication Skills
- · Military Experience
- Leadership
- DoD Experience
- Conflict Management
- Equipment Repair
- Troubleshooting
- Microsoft Excel
- English
- · Problem-solving
- Flexibility
- Team Work
- Reliability
- Technical Support
- Desktop Support
- Research & Development
- QA/QC (4 years)
- Live Chat
- Help Desk
- IT Support
- Project Management
- Quality Control
- · Microsoft SharePoint

- Microsoft Windows
- Remote Access Software

Military Service

Branch: United States Army

Rank: E-4/SPC

Awards

ARCOM

2019

Army Commendation Medal

AAM

2018

Army Achievement Medal

AAM

2017

Army Achievement Medal

Certifications and Licenses

CJIS Security Awareness Training: Level 4

June 2020 to May 2024